okay great so I'm going to give a talk
很好，我要讲一个
that has a lot of JavaScript in it
里面有很多JavaScript
sometimes that gets a reaction like boo
有时会得到类似嘘的反应
you know the how how many you guys have
你知道你们有多少人
to work with JavaScript on a regular
定期使用JavaScript
basis this is the case everywhere right
根据这是无处不在的情况
and um but people say oh I'm a Java
和嗯，但是人们说我是Java
developer JavaScript is bad language the
开发人员JavaScript是错误的语言
what I'm going to try and talk about in
我将要尝试谈论的内容
this talk is that that assumption that
这个话题是那个假设
mindset it's kind of an illusion right
心态是一种错觉
everybody is have it everybody has to
每个人都有它，每个人都必须
work with JavaScript these days because
这些天使用JavaScript，因为
it's everywhere it's in the browser so
它在浏览器中无处不在，所以
and what I want to do is introduce some
我想做的是介绍一些
things to in this talk but challenge
在这次谈话中要做的事情，但充满挑战
your assumptions about whether
您对是否
JavaScript even is or isn't part of the
JavaScript甚至是或不属于
Java environment so we'll talk about
Java环境，所以我们将讨论
that I'm going to talk about web
我将要谈论网络
extensions how many of you guys have
扩展你们有多少人
heard of web extensions okay I'm going
听说网络扩展了，我要走了
to get into what those are and how they
弄清楚它们是什么以及它们如何
work and I'm also going to talk about
工作，我也要谈
isomorphic applications how many people
同构应用多少人
have heard of this concept so isomorphic
听说过这个概念，所以同构
applications just means getting your
应用程序只是意味着获取您的
code to run in multiple environments so
代码在多个环境中运行
the and then finally I'm going to talk
然后最后我要谈
about the project I'm working on with
关于我正在处理的项目
Mozilla and what it's about and filter
Mozilla及其相关内容和过滤条件
bubbles and we can talk about that and
气泡，我们可以谈谈
then I have some robot stuff that I work
然后我有一些可以工作的机器人东西
on it's just kind of fun and cool I know
我知道那只是一种乐趣和酷
do you guys want the the robot stuff is
你们想要机器人的东西吗
like three minutes of interesting robot
像三分钟有趣的机器人
videos do you want at the beginning or
您想在一开始播放视频还是
the end with beginning beginning okay
以开始开始结束
great
大
sorry I'm hard of hearing too many rock
对不起，我很难听到太多摇滚
shows let's see here so I was roommates
节目让我们看看这里，所以我是室友
in college with a guy named Dave Hanson
在大学里和一个叫戴夫·汉森的家伙
who's become famous for making super
谁因制造超级而出名
realistic robots I'm going to show you
现实的机器人，我将向您展示
some of those and then I'll show you a
其中一些，然后我会告诉你
current video with Jimmy Fallon viewers
吉米·法伦（Jimmy Fallon）观众的最新视频
anybody like Jimmy Fallon here so I'm
像吉米·法伦这样的人在这里，我
going to show the Sofia robot on Jimmy
将在吉米展示索非亚机器人
Fallon then I'll show you a development
法伦，然后我会告诉你发展
video from 2014 in Hong Kong just to
2014年香港的录像带
show you kind of how things how quickly
告诉你事情如何快速
things moved along
事情进展
you know where you are of course I'm in
你知道你当然在哪里
New York City and I'm on my favorite
我最喜欢纽约市
show The Tonight Show sure what jeez
节目《今晚》，请确保知道什么
could never be yours
永远不会是你的
nacho cheese that's a really fun thing
玉米片奶酪真的很有趣
to work on right there's a lot of stuff
在正确的地方工作很多
going on inside Sophia there's there's
在索菲亚里面，那里有
about 40 motors in there that you've got
那里大约有40台电动机
to control there are real time message
控制有实时消息
bus message queue kind of things going
总线消息队列中发生的事情
on to control all that there is voice
来控制所有声音
synthesis voice recognition then the
然后合成语音识别
voice recognition you know pro city
你知道的语音识别专业城市
emotional content analysis there's a lot
情感内容分析有很多
of stuff that you get a play with trying
您可以尝试的东西
to build a system like this it's kind of
建立这样的系统
like Alexa right but you're then trying
像Alexa一样，但是您正在尝试
to extend beyond that and get it you
超越并获得它
don't think about your face as a user
不要以用户身份考虑自己的脸
interfaces but you know or your arms
界面，但您知道或怀抱
your hands or gestures but all of these
你的手或手势，但所有这些
things are very meaningful you know to a
事情对你很有意义
person we have these very sophisticated
人，我们有这些非常老练的人
rules we've built up about how we
关于我们如何建立的规则
communicate with each other and it's
彼此交流，这是
interesting to program it because you
编程很有趣，因为您
have to really become conscious of all
必须真正意识到所有
these things so when Dave and days we
这些事情，所以当戴夫和我们在一起时
doing this stuff for a long time but
做了很长时间但
their animation platform previously was
他们的动画平台以前是
more like the kind of system that let's
更像是让我们
say you had a assembly line automation
说你有流水线自动化
and you're trying to control an arm
而您正在尝试控制手臂
putting lids on applesauce you know
在你知道的苹果酱上盖上盖子
going by on a conveyor belt that was
在一条传送带上经过
kind of like more what they were using
有点像他们正在使用的东西
so each but in that face there are
所以每个，除了那张脸
dozens of motors controlling pulleys and
数十个控制皮带轮的电动机和
you know that mimic the tendons and
你知道模仿肌腱和
other structures in your face so a motor
脸上的其他结构，例如马达
like pull the cord that pulls a net
就像拉网的绳子一样
that's fused into the Hat
融合到帽子里
rubber rubber that Dave developed that
戴夫开发的橡胶
creates these you know different
创建这些你知道不同的东西
expressions right so Dave and his team
表达正确，所以戴夫和他的团队
we're having to go in and on a timeline
我们必须进入时间表
just each motor basically you had a yet
基本上每个马达都有一个
a graph representing the motor position
代表电动机位置的图表
and they had to painstakingly position
他们不得不辛苦地摆姿势
each of those things well in a Disney
在迪士尼，这些东西都很好
movie or like a Pixar movie there's a
电影或类似皮克斯电影的电影
way more mature set of tour tools for
方式更成熟的一套旅游工具
doing emotional animation and how many
做情感动画以及多少
you guys have ever used blender or Maya
你们曾经用过搅拌机或玛雅人
or any of these kinds of tools so
或任何这类工具
blender is a amazing piece of free
搅拌器是一个了不起的免费工具
software that gives you a really robust
使您真正强大的软件
set of tools for building awesome
一套很棒的工具
animations and I talked to Dave and said
动画，我和戴夫交谈，说
you know you guys should be using this
你知道你们应该用这个
we could write a binding layer between
我们可以在
the animation tools and the and the
动画工具以及
motor control in the robot operating
机器人操作中的电机控制
system so has anybody ever heard of the
系统，所以没有人听说过
robot operating system Ross so Ross does
机器人操作系统罗斯，罗斯也这样做
some really cool things it is like an
一些非常酷的东西就像
operating system for robotics right
机器人权利操作系统
robot operating systems so what does
机器人操作系统怎么办
that mean at an operating system
这意味着在操作系统上
provides a layer of abstraction between
提供了一层之间的抽象
your program and your peripherals so for
您的程序和外围设备
instance let's say in the early days
比方说，在早期
early early word processors like a Wang
像Wang一样的早期早期文字处理程序
word processor an IBM word processor
文字处理器IBM文字处理器
Wang word processor could work on a Wang
王文字处理器可以在王上工作
printer and in fact maybe just even a
打印机，实际上甚至只是一个
specific Wang printer so literally the
特定的王打印机所以字面上的
word processor in its code had the
其代码中的文字处理器具有
control codes for this specific printer
此特定打印机的控制代码
you couldn't take an IBM printer and put
你不能带一台IBM打印机放
it on your Wang word processor or vice
将其放在您的Wang文字处理器上或副
versa because they were written
反之亦然，因为它们是书面的
specifically to work with each other and
专门互相合作
when operating systems got more mature
当操作系统变得更加成熟时
they provided an abstraction layer so
他们提供了一个抽象层
you had you know this idea of a document
您知道文档的这种想法
that needed to be printed you know word
需要打印的你知道单词
or your word processor manipulates a
或您的文字处理器操纵一个
document and it says hey operating
文档，它说嘿操作
system print this for me and the
系统为我和
operating system takes care of
操作系统照顾
translating that abstract idea of a
翻译的抽象概念
document into the control codes to
文件成控制码
control the printer so Ross does this
控制打印机，以便Ross做到这一点
for
对于
robotics concepts so for instance
例如，机器人技术
there's a two major kinds of motors a
有两种主要的电动机
servo motor and a stepper motor a servo
伺服电机和步进电机
motor has a single control line usually
电机通常只有一条控制线
and it uses the timing of the pulses on
它使用脉冲的定时
the control line to set the position the
控制线设置位置
rotational position of the motor a
电机的旋转位置
stepper motor has multiple control lines
步进电机有多条控制线
and manipulates this by activating the
并通过激活
lines in series also sets the rotation
串联的线也设置旋转
of the motor your if you're writing a
电机的功率，如果您正在编写
program you don't really care how that
程序你并不在乎
all works you just say I have a
所有的作品，你只是说我有一个
rotational joint I want it to be at 45
旋转关节，我希望它在45岁
degrees and then the Ross takes care of
度，然后罗斯照顾
the translation between that abstract
该摘要之间的翻译
idea of a rotating motor and the
旋转电机和
physical reality of manipulating some
操作一些的物理现实
specific piece of hardware so I wrote a
特定的硬件，所以我写了一个
binding layer that would take the
绑定层将
animation rig in blender and then
在Blender中制作动画装备，然后
connect it to the Ross abstract concepts
将其连接到罗斯抽象概念
of motors so that then it could drive
电机，以便它可以驱动
the actual motors in Sofia's head so I
索非亚头脑中真正的马达，所以我
have a small contracting company in
在有一个小型订约公司
Dallas you know kind of size business
达拉斯，您知道某种规模的企业
you know maybe any you guys could start
你知道也许你们可以开始
we have four employees but we do all
我们有四个员工，但我们都做
kinds of different things most of what
大部分不同的东西
we do that for the to make the rent IR
我们这样做是为了使租金IR
is to build erp systems usually on
通常是在
apache open for business and usually
apap营业，通常
with a modern JavaScript front-end so i
与现代的JavaScript前端，所以我
do i spend a lot of time writing java
我花很多时间写Java吗
and writing javascript and but i did
和编写JavaScript，但我做到了
have an interesting piece of work come
有一件有趣的工作来
in that mozilla wanted me to help with
在那个Mozilla想要我帮助
helped them do something with filter
帮助他们做一些过滤器
bubbles which is kind of the you know
你知道的那种泡沫
whole fake news news kind of the just
整个假新闻新闻的公正
medium modern media and trying to build
中等现代媒体并试图建立
tools to help users understand what's
帮助用户了解内容的工具
going on in modern media and to
在现代媒体和
demonstrate the new web extensions api
演示新的Web扩展API
so what our web extensions web
那么我们的网络扩展网站
extensions are a new api that was a
扩展程序是一个新的api
collaboration originally between Mozilla
Mozilla之间最初的合作
and Google Chrome to allow you to write
和谷歌浏览器，使您可以编写
plug-ins for the browser using
浏览器的插件使用
a script to write the code and HTML to
编写代码和HTML的脚本
build your user interfaces so instead of
建立您的用户界面，而不是
C++ and xpcom and kind of all these
C ++和xpcom以及所有这些
browsers like the internal
内部浏览器
implementation specific details of a
具体实施细节
browser you have this very high level
浏览器您具有很高的水平
programming environment that's pretty
漂亮的编程环境
much like what you're used to already
很像你已经习惯的
building normal web pages with
使用构建普通网页
JavaScript it lets you add new buttons
JavaScript，可让您添加新按钮
to the toolbar in the browser and you
到浏览器中的工具栏，您
know this this is just an HTML page and
知道这只是一个HTML页面，
then you can do all kinds of stuff that
然后你可以做各种各样的事情
you can't do from a normal web page it
你不能从普通网页上做
lets you you know you can monitor user
让您知道可以监视用户
activity you can watch what all the tabs
活动中您可以观看所有标签
in the browser what pages they're on you
在浏览器中他们在您的页面上
can tell when they change pages you can
可以告诉他们何时更改页面
get a call back when somebody switches
有人切换时回电
pages you can look at the content in you
您可以在其中查看内容的页面
look at the Dom of every window that's
看看每个窗户的
open in the browser you can see the
在浏览器中打开，您可以看到
history of the browser you can see the
浏览器的历史记录，您可以看到
bookmarks you can manipulate the
您可以操作的书签
bookmarks you can create bookmarks you
您可以创建书签
can you basically lets you control the
基本上可以让您控制
browser you know and way more control
您知道的浏览器并能更好地控制
way more access than you have from
方式比您拥有的更多
within a page context and it's it
在页面上下文中就可以了
currently is I'm not going to say it's a
目前我不会说这是一个
hundred percent portable right that I
我的百分之一百便携式
mean it's not exactly like you write the
意思是不完全像你写的那样
same piece of JavaScript exactly and it
完全一样的JavaScript，
will run across Firefox Chrome Opera and
将在Firefox Chrome Opera和
edge but it is like 95 98% there and
边缘，但那里好像是95 98％
there are more and more libraries
有越来越多的图书馆
there's already a number of libraries
已经有很多图书馆
that create polyfills
创建polyfills
right which is an adapter class
对，这是一个适配器类
essentially that mostly smooth out any
基本上可以平滑任何
of the remaining differences so already
剩下的差异，所以已经
with a few libraries you can reliably
有了一些库，您可以可靠地
write a single javascript HTML piece of
写一个javascript HTML
code and plug it into all four of these
代码并将其插入所有这四个
browsers right and add on to any of
浏览器，然后添加到任何
these browsers and that's a really
这些浏览器，这真的是
powerful concept and so the structure
强大的概念等结构
one of these things looks basically like
这些事情之一基本上像
this you have a you have a manifest file
这个你有一个清单文件
that sets up the different components
设置不同的组件
you typically then have a couple of
您通常会有几个
different UI elements so you'd have your
不同的UI元素，因此您将拥有
that pop-up you have a pop-up HTML and a
该弹出窗口有一个弹出HTML和一个
pop-up j/s so just like building a web
弹出j / s，就像建立网站一样
page
页
you also I don't have it here but you
你也我没有，但是你
can also create options pages so just
也可以创建选项页面
like if you've used any of your plugins
就像您使用过任何插件一样
and you go to settings and it brings you
然后您进入设置，它带给您
to a separate page where you can control
到一个您可以控制的单独页面
the settings for that plug-in that it
该插件的设置
lets you do that kind of stuff but then
让你做那种事情，但是
you also have a background contact
您也有背景联系人
script that when the browser kicks off
浏览器启动时的脚本
it'll run your background script and you
它会运行您的后台脚本，您
can start processes then that run
可以启动流程然后运行
continuously in the background all the
一直在后台
time the pop-up basically every time you
基本上每次您都会弹出时间
pop that pop up and then let it close
弹出，然后关闭
it's as if you've reloaded the page so
就像您已重新加载页面一样
the state resets every time but the
状态每次都会重置，但
state of the background script it's
后台脚本的状态是
there all the time and you also then
一直在那里，然后你也
have content scripts and what the
有内容脚本以及
content scripts do is that when any page
内容脚本要做的是，当任何页面
is opened in the browser it basically it
基本上是在浏览器中打开的
lets you inject your own JavaScript into
让您将自己的JavaScript注入
the JavaScript environment of that page
该页面的JavaScript环境
and you can add additional listeners you
您可以添加其他监听器
can manipulate the document so you know
可以操纵文档，所以您知道
you could be like you could you can put
你可能就像你可以放
a Content script in there that goes oh
在那里的内容脚本哦
am I in the Google web page context okay
我在Google网页环境中可以吗
I'm going to make the search field blue
我将搜索字段设为蓝色
and any time you went to Google on that
而且任何时候你去谷歌
machine and opened it the search field
机器并打开它的搜索字段
would be blue so you can you can do
会是蓝色的，所以你可以做
anything right it's it lets you add
没关系，它可以让您添加
JavaScript to any page that's your
JavaScript到您的任何页面
JavaScript so with that in mind let's
JavaScript，因此请记住
talk about isomorphic applications a
谈论同构应用
little bit the so what did you do with
一点点，那你怎么办
one of these web extensions right well
这些网络扩展之一非常合适
let's say you've got your Java you know
假设您拥有Java，
enterprise tool you know they're your
您知道他们是您的企业工具
company and you want to have something
公司，你想拥有一些东西
easily that when a sales lead comes in
轻松地找到销售线索
all the time when your sales guys can
一直在您的销售人员可以
just hit a button and here's your form
只需按一个按钮，这就是您的表格
to fill in a new sales leave um it goes
填写新的销售假期
up to your up to your to your Java
取决于您，取决于您的Java
server the or let's say you have two
服务器或假设您有两个
legacy applications right how many times
旧版应用程序运行了多少次
have you had this and you have to open
你有这个吗，你必须打开
something in some page and a legacy
某些页面中的内容和旧版
application somebody's actually sitting
实际坐在某人的应用程序
there in another tab and keying it in
在另一个选项卡中并将其键入
well you could make an extension that
好吧，你可以扩展一下
you know can see oh I've got I see
你知道可以看到哦，我知道了
you've got the old order application
你有旧订单申请
open and you're trying to enter in the
打开，您正在尝试输入
new order and it could just reach in
新订单，它可能会达到
pull the data out of the one and paste
从一个中拉出数据并粘贴
it into the other form
变成另一种形式
so then the user could look at it and go
这样用户就可以查看并继续
that's right hit submit instead of
那是正确的提交而不是
having to rekey everything well I mean
我必须重新整理好一切
lots of opportunity right anytime you
随时都有很多机会
want to all of a sudden reach into two
想要一下子变成两个
pages or anything like that you can you
页面或类似的内容，您可以
can do that so how many how many of you
可以做到，你们有多少人
have had to write JavaScript form
必须编写JavaScript表单
validation code alright so one of the
验证码很好，所以其中之一
things I want to challenge you to think
我想挑战你的事情
about as I go through this talk is how
在我进行本演讲时，关于
much could you reuse that exact same
你能重用完全一样的东西吗
validation logic inside your java
Java内部的验证逻辑
application there's so there's more and
应用程序，所以还有更多
more tools to do this kind of thing one
更多工具来做这种事情之一
of the classics is Rhino that's been
其中最经典的是犀牛
around a long time but in Java and in
大约很长一段时间，但在Java和
the VM now standard in the VM there's a
VM现在是VM中的标准配置
tool called nashorn anybody use national
名为nashorn的工具，任何人都可以使用
one so national arne is a much more
因此，全国范围内的敌人更多
high-performance JavaScript environment
高性能JavaScript环境
that's built into your JVM all the time
一直内置在JVM中
I'm going to talking to that but there's
我要说的是，但是有
also things like closure script which if
还有像关闭脚本这样的东西，如果
you're writing closure you can compile
你正在写闭包，你可以编译
closure into JavaScript with closure
闭包到JavaScript中
script but there's also J sweet which J
脚本，但也有J sweet，其中J
sweet you can write standard Java and it
不错，您可以编写标准的Java及其它
will compile your Java into JavaScript
将您的Java编译成JavaScript
that you can then put into your browser
然后可以放入浏览器
pages so what about Nashua Nash born
那么Nashua Nash的出生
like I said it's the JD kaise JavaScript
就像我说的是JD kaise JavaScript
solution ship standard in in the JDK in
解决方案运送标准在JDK中
the Java VM so they're all the time and
Java VM，因此它们一直都在
their Oracle is putting serious effort
他们的甲骨文正在认真努力
into making it high-performance in you
使其成为高性能
know in Java 7 you had invoke dynamic
知道在Java 7中您已经调用了动态
there's there's improvements going in in
有改进的地方
every Java release to improve the
每个Java版本以改进
performance of nashorn I won't tell you
我不会告诉你nashorn的表现
that it's at parity with nodejs
它与nodejs平价
but the gap is closing in many
但差距在缩小
situations it's going to perform you
情况会影响你
know close to no js' but it you know the
知道几乎没有js'，但您知道
big difference with it is you're in the
最大的不同是你在
java vm so you have access to facilities
java vm，因此您可以访问设施
in the java vm that just don't exist in
在不存在的java vm中
node.js room right no js' doesn't have
node.js房间对，没有js没有
threads right there are no threads for
线程正确，没有线程
for node.js so anything you do with a
for node.js，因此您可以使用
it's you know sending data back and
你知道回传数据，
forth between workers you have to send
您必须派遣工人之间来回
essentially message objects and past day
本质上是消息对象和过去的一天
by value but you know let's say you have
按价值计算，但您知道我们拥有
something like the disrupter ring buffer
破坏者环形缓冲区之类的东西
right which is a super high performance
对，这是超高性能
Java ring buffer structure it's used a
Java环形缓冲区的结构
lot like some stock trading applications
很像一些股票交易应用程序
use it if you've got an 8 gigabyte
如果您有8 GB，请使用它
in-memory data structure that you're
您正在使用的内存中数据结构
sharing between a bunch of threads that
在一堆线程之间共享
the threads are simultaneously
线程是同时的
manipulating that you can't go handing
操纵你不能去处理
an 8 gig object between workers right so
工人之间有8个演出对象
you can do things with javascript in the
您可以在
java vm that you just can't even do in
您甚至无法做到的Java虚拟机
nodejs right just not even possible so
正确的nodejs甚至不可能
apples to apples performance comparison
苹果与苹果的性能比较
is hard to make because the facilities
很难制造，因为设施
are simply not there and how easy is it
根本不在那儿，这有多容易
to get going so these two lines kind of
开始，所以这两行
show you a super simple example of doing
给你展示一个超简单的例子
a little JavaScript the you get asked
一些JavaScript，你会被问到
for a new script engine from the script
用于脚本中的新脚本引擎
engine manager you ask for it by name
您按名称要求的引擎管理员
Nashorn and then here you go engine eval
Nashorn，然后在这里进行引擎评估
and you can put any JavaScript you want
你可以放任何你想要的JavaScript
in there and it'll run it it will
在里面，它将运行它将
convert it to Java bytecode and execute
将其转换为Java字节码并执行
it but you can not only you know spit
它，但你不仅可以知道吐
something to standard out if you
如果您要标准化一些东西
instantiate an object in JavaScript here
在此处用JavaScript实例化对象
and return that you're going to get back
并返回您将要回来
an object handle in Java that you can
Java中的对象句柄
call methods on and you can even pass
调用方法，甚至可以传递
Java objects into and have that
Java对象进入并拥有
JavaScript object call methods on your
您的JavaScript对象调用方法
Java object and that it all works
Java对象，一切正常
seamlessly right it's all just more
无缝地对所有的一切
objects in the Java VM so that's one of
Java VM中的对象，这是
the things I want you guys to think
我要你们思考的事情
about is don't think about it as like
关于是不要像这样想
there's JavaScript world in Java world
Java世界中有JavaScript世界
Java is a human language the Java VM
Java是人类语言Java VM
does not run Java source code right it
不能运行Java源代码
runs Java bytecode
运行Java字节码
well Nashorn compiles JavaScript into
Nashorn将JavaScript编译成
Java bytecode so javascript with Nashorn
Java字节码所以Nashorn的JavaScript
is just another way to produce Java
只是产生Java的另一种方式
bytecode so if you have already have
字节码，所以如果您已经有
validation logic if you already have
验证逻辑（如果您已经拥有）
value in your existing JavaScript that
现有JavaScript中的价值
you've had to write for web applications
您必须为Web应用程序编写
before you rewrite it in Java take a
在用Java重写之前，请先
step back and go like can we just use
退后一步，就像我们可以使用
that do we have to rewrite that and
那我们必须重写它，并且
really think about that right because if
真的考虑那个权利，因为如果
you get in the position of that you're
你的位置是
not only doing your validation logic
不仅要执行验证逻辑
let's say in in your web application
假设在您的Web应用程序中
but now you're talking about doing an
但是现在您正在谈论做一个
iOS native app and you're talking about
iOS原生应用，您正在谈论
doing an Android native app you know
做一个您知道的Android本机应用程序
that you're going to have to keep your
你将不得不保持你的
Objective C version of that validation
验证的目标C版本
like logic your java version of that
就像逻辑上那样
validation logic your javascript version
验证逻辑您的JavaScript版本
of that validation logic that's all
验证逻辑的全部
engineering hours and those are all
工程时间，这些都是
opportunities for failure right you can
失败的机会就可以
have drift between your versions and
在您的版本和
that's how you get serious bugs in your
这就是您遇到严重错误的方式
platform so you want to you know don't
平台，所以您想知道不
repeat yourself single source of truth
重复自己的真相
can you reuse that code and that's what
您可以重用该代码吗？
that's what isomorphic applications are
这就是同构应用
about it's Ekman script 5 I think
关于它，我认为是埃克曼剧本5
there's some ACMA script 6 coming but
还有一些ACMA脚本6，但是
you can you know like you can run
你可以知道你可以跑步
express with babel like you can use
像巴贝尔一样表达
webpack and babel and produce with the
webpack和babel并使用
transpiler that will work on nashua so
可以在nashua上运行的转译器
you can use echo script 6 constructs
您可以使用echo脚本6构造
they're just transpiled so there's some
他们只是被转译，所以有一些
performance considerations but like I
性能方面的考虑，但和我一样
said natural one is definitely under
说自然的肯定在
active development Oracle is definitely
积极发展Oracle绝对是
gets it the JavaScript in Java is a big
得到它Java中的JavaScript很大
deal and they are pursuing that because
交易，他们追求，因为
you know the reality is for Java and the
您知道现实是Java和
browser applets are gone right nobody's
浏览器小程序正确无人
even thinking about I mean before there
甚至想着我的意思是在那之前
and now that even that they're
现在，即使他们是
officially gone nobody was really that
正式走了，没有人真的是
happy about using applets for a while
很高兴一段时间使用小程序
now so the web is just getting to be a
现在，网络正逐渐成为
bigger and bigger deal and javascript is
越来越大的交易和JavaScript是
everywhere you know with and with tools
借助工具了解的任何地方
like PhoneGap Apache Cordova anybody
像PhoneGap Apache Cordova一样
ever play with that you can you can
曾经玩过，你可以
build a simple web application and
构建一个简单的Web应用程序并
package it for the web store you can put
将其打包到您可以放置​​的网上商店
it into the Apple Store put it in the
将其放入Apple Store中
Android store so there's these powerful
Android商店，所以这些功能强大
platforms that are emerging to let you
新兴平台让您
move your code between all kinds of
在各种代码之间移动代码
different environments you can get
您可以获得的不同环境
nodejs kind of style work with yeah
nodejs风格与yeah合作
yes yes so you can you should be able to
是的，所以你应该可以
call any method on any java object from
从中调用任何Java对象上的任何方法
javascript using Nashorn so anything you
使用Nashorn的javascript
could write in Java I believe and I
我相信我可以用Java编写
believe you should be able to minute you
相信你应该能够打动你
can do things like manipulate threads
可以做诸如操纵线程之类的事情
from JavaScript in using Nashorn like
从JavaScript中使用Nashorn
you know if you have a handle to those
你知道你是否有能力
objects you can call you just you can
你可以打电话给你的东西
call methods on Java objects so anything
Java对象上的调用方法
you can do via calling methods on Java
您可以通过在Java上调用方法来完成
objects you may you may have to do some
您可能需要做的事情
casting you may have to go depending on
取决于您的铸造
like if you try to do something really
例如，如果您尝试真正做某事
low-level I don't have a Pat answer in
低级别的我没有Pat的答案
terms of you know will it be easy but
你知道的话会很容易，但是
you should be anything you can do in
你应该做任何你能做的
Java you should be able to do in
您应该能够使用的Java
JavaScript there may be some like there
JavaScript可能有一些类似的东西
may be some interesting things when it
可能是一些有趣的事情
comes to getting if you have like you
如果你喜欢你就会得到
know a method that you're using casting
知道您正在使用转换的方法
you know to that the type detection
你知道类型检测
plays a big role in it it may get a
在其中扮演重要角色，可能会
little complicated but so you may have
有点复杂，但您可能会有
to do something like write an adapter
做类似写适配器的事情
class in Java that like gives JavaScript
Java中的类，它提供了JavaScript
little help in hand just to understand
几乎没有什么帮助，只是为了了解
the typing system so and you know
打字系统，所以你知道
there's because there's so much
因为有太多
happening with JavaScript there is a lot
JavaScript发生了很多
of evolution happening in the JavaScript
JavaScript中发生的进化
space with things very sophisticated
空间非常复杂
concepts that are hot in the Java space
Java领域的热门概念
right the same kind of ideas like
对像这样的想法
immutable operative script callback
不可变的操作脚本回调
oriented programming in JavaScript is
JavaScript中的面向程序设计是
very very sophisticated so like Java
非常非常复杂，就像Java
programmers are kind of just now
程序员只是现在
discovering lambdas and how to deal with
发现lambda以及如何处理
them well javascript has been thinking
他们很好的JavaScript一直在思考
that way for a long time and you know
这种方式很长一段时间，你知道
like a big reason that asynchronous IO
就像异步IO的一个重要原因
is in Java right everybody kind of
在Java中，每个人都可以
remembers the history is no jazz came
记得历史上没有爵士乐来过
out of nowhere all of a sudden and for
突然间
for huge numbers of simultaneous
大量同时
sessions node.js was just hand in Java
会话node.js只是Java语言
you know hand in Java it's but you know
你知道用Java写的，但是你知道
because it
因为它
and it wasn't that nodejs produces way
并不是nodejs产生了方式
faster code right it's just it's a way
更快的代码，这只是一种方式
different strategy because if you have
不同的策略，因为如果你有
10,000 simultaneous sessions on the old
10,000个旧会话同时进行
servlet structure you have 10,000
您有10,000个servlet结构
threads but on no js' you have 10,000
线程，但没有js'，则有10,000个
callbacks sitting in an array with a
坐在一个数组中的回调
thread iterating over those and seeing
线程遍历那些并看到
if data is ready and then just go and
如果数据准备好了，那就去
here's some data here's some data here's
这是一些数据这是一些数据
some data so that getting rid of that
一些数据，以便摆脱
overhead of all those threads is that's
所有这些线程的开销是
why they did async i/o you know and now
他们为什么不进行异步输入输出
Java has very good performance so now
Java具有非常好的性能，所以现在
that people are using those kinds of
人们正在使用那种
techniques that mostly came from the
技术主要来自
JavaScript space in the Java VM you can
您可以在Java VM中使用JavaScript空间
get back to parity and performance so
回到平价和性能上
there's a lot of stuff going on around
有很多事情发生
callback oriented programming in
面向回调的编程
JavaScript that you may find it's
您可能会发现的JavaScript
actually easier to write it in
实际上更容易写
JavaScript or that there's more mature
JavaScript还是更成熟
tools available in JavaScript because
JavaScript中提供的工具，因为
things like you know already remembers
像你知道的事情已经记住了
when you first were doing you know
当你第一次做的时候你知道
dollar sign get and you had your success
美元符号得到，你就成功了
callback like let's say you're trying to
回调，比如说您正在尝试
call a series of rest services in order
依次致电一系列休息服务
and you're having to you're having to
而且你必须要
nest on one inside the other right you
嵌套在另一个里面就对了
get these kind of crazy flying V's in
得到这些疯狂的飞V
your code well people in JavaScript land
您的代码精通JavaScript的人们
got sick of that and that's where the
厌倦了那个，那是
then you know then operator came from
那么你知道操作员是从哪里来的
and things that you could then if I
还有我可以做的事情
where you're saying I want to call this
你在说我想叫这个
and then when that's done I want then I
然后当我想要的时候
want this function to be called and then
希望此函数被调用，然后
I want this function to be called and
我想调用此函数，然后
you can have very clean code for doing
您可以使用非常干净的代码
these kinds of nested callback oriented
这些面向嵌套的回调
structures and it's a different way of
结构，这是一种不同的方式
thinking so spending some time in the
思考，所以花一些时间在
JavaScript space with these libraries
这些库的JavaScript空间
will really up your game for using
确实会提高您的游戏使用能力
lambdas in Java because it's conceptual
Java中的lambda，因为它是概念性的
right it's not just it's not about the
对，这不只是关于
language it's a concept just like for
语言是一个概念，就像
loops or if you know any programming
循环或您是否知道任何编程
concept it's really about the concepts
概念真的是关于概念
because those it's easy to learn if you
因为那些很容易学习，如果你
understand a concept it's easy to go to
理解一个概念很容易
a new language and understand and learn
一种新的语言，理解和学习
that concept in a new language if you
如果您使用新的语言，该概念
don't understand the concept then that's
不明白这个概念，那就是
what's hard to learn
什么很难学
so I'm doing some work with react how
所以我正在做一些反应
many people are working will react or
很多人在工作会做出反应或
redux so this is like this is an example
redux，所以这就像一个例子
of some really cool concepts that can be
一些非常酷的概念
applied in the Java space but it's about
应用在Java空间中，但是
the conceptual framework so in a react
这样的概念框架
app location State is immutable you have
应用程序位置状态是不可变的
action objects that run that run through
运行的动作对象
things called reducers that atomically
原子称为减速器的东西
manipulate the state and because you
操纵国家，因为你
don't have threads in JavaScript it's
在JavaScript中没有线程
really an atomic situation that you have
确实是原子状态
a that you have a that you have a very
一个你有一个你有一个非常
predictable state transition I'm going
我要进行可预测的状态转换
to talk about that in a second slide
在第二张幻灯片中讨论
this is just to give you an example how
这只是给你一个例子
many people have written anything where
很多人在哪里写了什么
you do you know callback driven like
你知道回调驱动像
each swing you know swing programmers or
每个秋千，你知道秋千程序员或
just in JavaScript you know you go but
只是在JavaScript中，您就知道了，但是
button on click and you write a function
单击按钮，然后编写函数
and in that function right there maybe
在那个功能中
you do a jQuery get well if you have a
如果你有一个jQuery，你会做得很好
lot of this kind of stuff going on you
很多这样的东西在你身上
can have a pretty complicated
可能会很复杂
interactions between all the timing of
所有时间之间的相互作用
how these events happen right because
这些事件如何正确发生，因为
you you think you're going to be able to
你以为你将能够
do that jQuery get and it's going to
做到jQuery的，它将
come back in a particular order but like
按特定顺序回来，但喜欢
the if you are assuming that's always
如果您假设这总是
going to happen with certain timing that
将会在一定的时间发生
can get real complicated and debugging
会变得非常复杂和调试
that understanding what's going on can
理解正在发生的事情可以
get very complicated so what happens in
变得非常复杂，所以发生了什么
with redux and in react is when you
与redux和反应是当你
trigger an event initially it it never
最初不会触发事件
you never do anything right then other
你永远不会做任何其他的事
than you create an object that
比您创建的对象
represents a request to do something and
代表要求做某事，
you essentially put it on a queue that's
你基本上把它放在一个队列中
going to get processed later outside of
稍后将在外面进行处理
your code in a deterministic way and
您的代码确定性地
then the the thing that actually
然后那个东西
processes that this is this is an action
流程，这是一个动作
event in react redux land and then later
在React Redux Land中发生事件，然后稍后
the action event processor you take you
您带给您的动作事件处理器
see that you're going to do this action
看到您将要执行此操作
and you take the state you make a copy
然后你把状态复制
of the state and you return a modified
状态，您返回修改后的
copy so this is side-effects free right
复制，所以这是副作用免费的权利
because you never directly manipulate a
因为你永远不会直接操纵一个
state you always copy the state and
说你总是复制状态和
return a new modified copy
返回新的修改后的副本
so I have some interesting side effects
所以我有一些有趣的副作用
because you have those action events end
因为你的动作事件结束了
up being like a player piano tape you
像个钢琴演奏者一样
could think of it like it's a mechanical
可以想像它是机械的
tape controlling your program you have
磁带控制您的程序
an action action action action and they
一个行动，一个行动，他们
happen in some order and it's very easy
以某种顺序发生，这很容易
you can audit right this stream of
您可以对此流进行审核
actions because it's actually just you
行动，因为实际上只是你
could think of it as an array of objects
可以将其视为对象数组
representing actions that your program
代表程序的动作
needs to take and they caused a series
需要采取，他们造成了一系列
of state transitions and because state
状态转换的原因在于
is always modified as a copy right the
总是被修改为版权
transition is all is very easy to
过渡非常容易
understand so let's say you got your
明白，所以假设您得到了
to-do list right you start out empty
待办事项列表正确，您一开始就是空的
to-do list add it to do two got a now
待办事项列表将其添加到执行两个操作中
estate with one to do add it to do two
一个要做的遗产加它做两个
to dus remove it to do back to one right
去删除它做回到右
this approach lets you do some very
这种方法可以让您做一些非常
interesting things in terms of testing
测试方面有趣的事情
in terms of debugging so like let's say
在调试方面，比如说
you put a feature toggle in your app
您在应用程序中放置了功能切换
where if you have a you know let's say
如果你有一个地方，你会说
you have users that are having problems
您有遇到问题的用户
with some facility you could turn on a
有一些设施，你可以打开一个
future toggle that you're going to
未来的切换
record the action that's a series of
记录一系列的动作
actions and when the error occurs here
动作以及何时发生错误
have pushed that series of action
推动了一系列行动
objects up to the server so then you can
对象到服务器，这样您就可以
pull that series of action objects down
下拉那一系列动作对象
to your development environment if you
您的开发环境
replay them if you write it correctly if
如果正确编写，请重播
you follow the rules you can playback
您遵循可以播放的规则
the users series of action objects and
用户系列的动作对象和
you'll get the exact same state right
您将获得完全相同的状态
it's deterministic which is funny you
确定性的，这很有趣
know that when things get complicated
知道事情变得复杂
you start going can it really still be
你开始走下去，真的还可以吗
deterministic if you if you have a
确定您是否拥有
computer program and it's deterministic
计算机程序及其确定性
no matter how complicated it is you can
不管它有多复杂
replay it and it mechanically you're
重播它，机械地你
going to get the same state so this lets
将获得相同的状态，所以这让
you do some pretty interesting things
你做一些有趣的事情
like let's say you well let's take this
就像说你很好，让我们接受这个
let's say you want to you want to test
假设您要测试
like you got at let's say it takes you
就像你说的那样，这需要你
hours of interactions to get to this
数小时的互动才能达到目的
state and then this is where your errors
状态，然后这就是您的错误所在
start happening well you could serialize
开始发生的很好，您可以序列化
this state you know you can then unpack
您知道可以打开包装的状态
that serialized state and start playing
序列化状态并开始播放
actions series of actions against it and
针对它的一系列动作和
you're again going to just be able to
您将再次能够
move forward from there so it lets you
从那里向前移动，它可以让您
like snapshot time time travel if you
例如快照时间，时间旅行
want to do undo right all you have
想要撤消就对了
to do to implement undo is you just snap
要执行撤消操作，您只是按一下
the application state back to the
应用状态回到
previous state and you're doing that
以前的状态，而您正在这样做
because the entire application state is
因为整个应用程序状态是
in a single state object that your whole
在单个状态对象中
app will just snap back into place you
应用程式会重新回到您的位置
know if you say undo that delete well
知道你是否说过撤消删除
there's two there's two to do objects
有两个有两个要做的对象
again so that's kind of what I covered
再次，这就是我所涵盖的
here but I think it's with easier with
在这里，但我认为这样更容易
the illustration yeah and for testing
是的，用于测试
again you know like you can have your
再一次，你知道你可以拥有你的
mock state that in your test environment
在测试环境中模拟状态
like to test your application you can
想测试您的应用程序，您可以
just restore this complicated user state
只需恢复此复杂的用户状态
that represents a long-term interaction
代表长期的互动
start playing it back from there instead
从那里开始播放
of having to always like replay all the
总是喜欢重播所有
way from the beginning kind of like in
从一开始就有点像
selenium so filter bubbler is a program
硒，所以滤泡器是一个程序
on is a web extension that I'm
上是我的网络扩展
implementing it's sponsored by Muslim
由穆斯林赞助实施
working with them and it is to let you
与他们合作，就是让你
is first of all to demonstrate the web
首先是演示网络
extensions API but then it's also to
扩展API，但随后
like let you analyze your web browsing
就像让您分析网页浏览
habits in kind of the same way that big
习惯也一样大
guides like Facebook and Google are
像Facebook和Google这样的指南
analyzing your web browsing habits right
正确分析您的网络浏览习惯
now and it's it's to let you visualize
现在，这是让你形象化
your filter bubble so what's a filter
你的滤泡，那么什么是滤镜
bubble filter bubble is really another
气泡过滤器气泡真的是另一个
word for cognitive bias right how many
认知偏见这个词对吧
people have heard this term cognitive
人们听过这个词认知
bias like cognitive bias an example
偏见，例如认知偏见
would be I'm a Java guy I'm supposed to
我应该是个Java的家伙
not like JavaScript review it is this
不像JavaScript评论是这样
other thing right it's a cognitive bias
没错，这是一种认知偏见
it's a set of assumptions that we see
这是我们看到的一组假设
the world through so sometimes those
通过世界有时
assumptions can be accurate like you you
假设可能像您一样准确
know shouldn't jump off a cliff
知道不应该跳下悬崖
sometimes they could just be things
有时他们可能只是事物
you've picked up along the way and
您一路走来，
that's you believe are true maybe
那是你认为是真的，也许
they're true maybe they're not so the
他们是真的，也许不是，
this has always been typical right we
这一直是典型的权利，我们
surround ourselves with people that we
与我们周围的人在一起
like we read magazines and newspapers
就像我们读杂志和报纸一样
about things that we like you know if we
关于我们喜欢你的事情，如果我们知道
like bicycling we read bicycling
就像骑自行车，我们读骑自行车
magazines we know a lot about bicycling
我们对骑自行车了解很多的杂志
we may not know about knitting so that's
我们可能不知道编织，所以
that's normal but now that search
那很正常，但是现在搜索
engines and social networks play such a
引擎和社交网络发挥着
dominant role in our lives these
这些在我们的生活中起着主导作用
organizations are you
组织是你
very sophisticated tools to monitor our
非常复杂的工具来监控我们的
behavior and take advantage of our
行为并利用我们的优势
cognitive biases to control our browsing
认知偏见来控制我们的浏览
habits so you know Facebook for instance
习惯，所以你知道例如Facebook
they're using the most sophisticated
他们正在使用最先进的
techniques available deep learning big
深度学习可用的技术
data all this I mean they invented a lot
记录所有这些，我的意思是他们发明了很多
of the big data stuff right why'd they
他们为什么会选择大数据呢？
do that well to analyze their users
很好地分析用户
behavior and to send you you inputs
行为并向您发送输入
theoretically that posts that you're
从理论上讲，您是
going to like the most right so that may
会喜欢最正确的，这样可能
be one of the key performance indicators
成为关键绩效指标之一
that they're using is how much you press
他们正在使用的是您按了多少
like but obviously they have some other
喜欢，但显然他们还有其他
things on their agenda they want to keep
他们想保留的事情在他们的议程上
you on the system they want your you
您在系统上他们想要您
know they want your time on Facebook to
知道他们想要您在Facebook上的时间
blast a long time so they can serve you
爆炸很长时间，他们可以为您服务
lots of ads they want you to click on
他们希望您点击很多广告
ads so if they notice that people with
广告，如果他们注意到
browsing habits like yours
像你这样的浏览习惯
click on certain kinds of ads they're
点击某些类型的广告
going to try to look in your you know
要尝试看看你知道的
friends and look for posts that look
朋友，寻找看起来像的帖子
similar to the kinds of posts that make
类似于发布的内容
people like you click on ads all right
像您这样的人可以点击广告
and we we don't have those tools
而且我们没有那些工具
ourselves to understand our own browsing
自己了解我们自己的浏览
habits and we can't even see these
习惯，我们甚至看不到这些
things right so that in some in some in
事情是正确的，所以在某些在某些
some cases these organizations
在某些情况下，这些组织
understand our behavior better than we
比我们更了解我们的行为
understand ourselves our own behavior
了解我们自己的行为
because they have a very sophisticated
因为它们非常复杂
knowledge so the goal of filter bubbler
知识，所以过滤器起泡器的目标
is to try to give us some tools to do
试图给我们一些工具去做
analysis on our own behavior so what
分析我们自己的行为
does filter bubbler do it's it's really
确实会过滤起泡器吗
an essence similar to a spam filter
类似于垃圾邮件过滤器的本质
right everybody uses a spam filter right
每个人都使用垃圾邮件过滤器
who use a spam filter in this room
谁在这个房间里使用垃圾邮件过滤器
everybody right you ever think about
你想过的每个人都对
what a spam filter does a spam filter
垃圾邮件过滤器做什么
you have handed a program that uses
您已经提交了一个使用
statistical analysis the authority to
统计分析权威
decide whether a message even reaches
决定消息是否到达
you right if you if it decides
如果决定的话，你说的对
statistically that that message it
从统计上讲该消息
matches spam it never makes it to your
匹配垃圾邮件，它永远不会进入您的
inbox that's an extremely powerful idea
收件箱是一个非常强大的主意
and the the accuracy is really
准确度确实是
impressive right spam filtering people
令人印象深刻的垃圾邮件过滤人员
to ninety-nine point nine nine nine
到九十九点九九九
eight percent
百分之八
probably accurate and if it wasn't that
可能是准确的，如果不是那样
accurate people wouldn't tolerate it but
准确的人不会容忍它，但是
what's interesting about spam filters is
垃圾邮件过滤器的有趣之处在于
they don't care that it's spam right
他们不在乎这是垃圾邮件对吗
it's purely a statistical analysis like
纯粹是统计分析
a simple Bayesian analysis mostly you're
简单的贝叶斯分析
taking your messages say breaking them
接受您的讯息说打破它们
up into groups of five words and you're
分成五个词，你就是
doing a statistical analysis of what
对什么进行统计分析
five word groups are present in what
五个单词组出现在什么
groups of messages so it doesn't care
邮件组，所以它不在乎
what the patterns are that you're trying
您正在尝试的模式是什么
to match and nor does it have to be one
匹配，也不必是一个
kind of pattern one bucket of patterns
一种模式一桶模式
you can for instance I I heard something
例如我可以听到一些东西
that kind of blew me away which is that
那种把我吹走的是
the way that they evaluate SAT essays
他们评估SAT论文的方式
now is they use Bayesian analysis so
现在他们使用贝叶斯分析了吗
they take and they make a corpora of
他们采取，他们使语料库
like these are well written essays these
像这些都是写得很好的论文
are poorly written essays and then they
是写得不好的论文，然后他们
just feed essays into this and just like
只是将论文输入到其中，就像
a spam filter it's got better than human
一个垃圾邮件过滤器，它比人类要好
accuracy gets like ninety-nine point
精度达到九十九点
nine nine eight percent accuracy of this
九九八成
is a dumb illiterate essay or this is a
是愚蠢的文盲文章，还是这是
well-written smart essay because bad
写得好，因为不好
grammar for instance is a it's a
例如语法是一个
statistical profile certain words are
统计资料中某些词是
used in syriza's that they shouldn't be
在syriza中使用，它们不应该
right that's bad grammar
对，那是不好的语法
so because you can do this with anything
所以因为你可以做任何事情
what filter Butler does is it lets you
巴特勒所做的过滤器是什么
create a series of text corpora which is
创建一系列的文本语料库
basically your labeling URLs so let's
基本上是您的标签网址，所以让我们
say real simple when you're just going
你刚走的时候说真的很简单
to go this page has awesome stuff on it
去这个页面上有很棒的东西
this page has stupid stuff on it you're
这个页面上有愚蠢的东西
going to build up a list of two lists of
将要建立两个清单的清单
URLs system is going to read the text of
网址系统将读取
those pages and build up a statistical
这些页面并建立统计数据
profile of awesomeness and stupidness
令人敬畏和愚蠢的形象
and so then you can the the whole system
这样您就可以整个系统
is pluggable so the source is pluggable
可插拔，因此源可插拔
the classifier classifier is pluggable
分类器分类器是可插入的
and then the output of the
然后输出
classification is pluggable so a simple
分类是可插入的，因此简单
version might look at the page you're
版本可能会查看您所在的页面
currently looking at pass it through the
目前正在看它通过
classifier have it compare it to the two
分类器将其与两者进行比较
corpora and then make the classification
然后进行语料库的分类
show up in the drop-down menu you say
显示在您说的下拉菜单中
this page is awesome for this page is
这个页面很棒，这个页面是
stupid but you could do other stuff
愚蠢的，但你可以做其他的事情
right
对
you could woops my keyboard
你可以敲我的键盘
you could have it that my source is the
你可以相信我的来源是
last year of my browsing history and my
我的浏览历史记录的最后一年和
sink is a full a new folder I'm going to
水槽是一个完整的新文件夹，我要去
create in my bookmarks so I could take
在我的书签中创建，以便我可以
my entire last year of browsing history
我整个过去的浏览历史记录
take each content of each page compare
将每个页面的每个内容进行比较
it for awesomeness or stupidness and in
它是为了令人敬畏或愚蠢，
a new folder have two folders under it
一个新文件夹下面有两个文件夹
awesome and stupid and my personal
真棒和愚蠢，我的个人
browsing history will be automatically
浏览历史将自动
separated into awesome and stupid think
陷入愚蠢和愚蠢的想法
about what that would take you to do
关于你将要做什么
that yourself to go through and evaluate
自己去经历和评估
your own year of history browsing
您自己的历史浏览年份
history to look for patterns in it like
在其中寻找模式的历史
that and the these classifications are
那和这些分类是
also pluggable and what we're working on
也可插拔，我们正在努力
initially is a we're going to write a
最初是一个，我们要写一个
Java server Java JavaScript server as
Java服务器Java JavaScript服务器为
well but I'm even doing a a wordpress
好吧，但我什至在做一个WordPress的
plugin so anybody with WordPress can set
插件，因此任何使用WordPress的人都可以设置
up their own little private
自己的小私人
classification server so that they and
分类服务器，以便他们和
their friends can work together to make
他们的朋友可以一起做
their own classifications of content and
他们自己的内容分类和
share those classifications and build
分享这些分类并建立
them up as a group so you could you know
他们作为一个小组，所以你可以知道
beyond like this simple example let's
除了这个简单的例子，让我们
say you could take the New York Times
说你可以接受《纽约时报》
like last five years of New York Times
就像《纽约时报》最近五年一样
stories and separate them by department
故事并按部门分开
so politics arts you know sports and so
所以你知道体育的政治艺术等等
then if you want to extract from the
然后，如果您想从
last year your browsing history all the
去年您的浏览历史记录
stuff that looked like you were looking
看起来像您正在寻找的东西
at a sports page you could again go
在体育页面上，您可以再次进入
through it and it would drop it into a
通过它，它会掉进一个
folder and you could go look in the
文件夹，您可以转到
sports folder and you'd see your pages
运动文件夹，您会看到自己的页面
that you visited that look like they're
您访问过的网站看起来像他们
about sports so that's that's basically
关于体育运动，那基本上就是
the idea we can do some QA
我们可以进行质量检查的想法
and I'm going to put these up so you can
我将把这些放起来，以便您可以
write down URLs if you want so that's
写下URL，如果需要的话
basically my talk and I'm happy to
基本上我的谈话，我很高兴
answer any questions
回答任何问题
[Applause]
[掌声]
yeah absolutely and you can oh
是的，绝对可以
absolutely you can do that
绝对可以的
so with react and redux you they they
因此，通过反应和还原你，他们他们
have a completely headless mode for
具有完全无头模式
server-side rendering and so like if you
服务器端渲染等，如果您
want to preload a cache with renderings
想要预加载渲染的缓存
of all your product pages so that when
您所有产品页面中的
you when somebody requests a product on
当有人要求产品时，您
your you know Java based website that
您知道基于Java的网站
you're sending the HTML as it would be
您正在发送HTML
rendered in their browser using the same
在浏览器中使用相同
templates on your server in Java to
Java中的服务器上的模板
generate them yeah you can definitely do
生成它们，是的，您绝对可以做到
that and to with Redux for instance you
并以Redux为例
can also just take completely not render
也可以完全不渲染
the HTML and use like if you just want
HTML并使用，如果您只想
to use the reducer logic and the action
使用减速器的逻辑和动作
stream in you can act you can totally do
你可以尽自己所能去做
that there where you just start pushing
在那里，你只是开始推动
into the state and you just don't attach
进入状态，你只是不依附
the view objects to it like that you can
视图可以像这样反对
also do that but no yet yes definitely
也这样做，但绝对不是
and you can do that not just with react
你不仅可以做出反应
but with several platforms like view
但是有几个平台，例如view
jeaious also will support that anybody
嫉妒也将支持任何人
else yeah
否则
same Pat you can use NPM you can
可以使用NPM的同一拍子
oh sorry again the for nodejs
哦，再次抱歉，for nodejs
you have the NPM universe of languages
您拥有NPM语言世界
you can run NPM using Nashorn and you
您可以使用Nashorn运行NPM，然后
can actually use run your grunt it
可以实际使用您的咕actually声
Nashorn is pretty much at this point
Nashorn现在差不多
where it's at API parity with node.js so
与node.js处于API奇偶校验的位置
there may be some performance
可能会有一些表现
differences but you can basically run
差异，但您基本上可以运行
the JavaScript libraries you can run in
您可以在其中运行的JavaScript库
node.js you can run in nashua so in if
您可以在nashua中运行的node.js，如果
you can just use NPM same tools that
您可以使用NPM相同的工具
you're already used to using to build
您已经习惯于构建
your applications that you run and with
您运行的应用程序
nashua if you do it through the script
nashua，如果您通过脚本执行
manager it tends to reconstruct the
经理，它倾向于重建
national and environment every time you
每次您的国家和环境
ask for a new instance you don't have to
要求一个新实例，您不必
do it that way you can instantiate and
以这种方式可以实例化并
you can instantiate a natural run JIT
您可以实例化自然运行JIT
compiling interpreter and you can keep
编译口译员，您可以继续
it in its state around so you don't have
它周围的状态，所以你没有
to have that behavior you just it's not
有那种行为，你只是不是
a one-liner
单线
yeah sure like so pro city is uh is like
是的，肯定像职业城市一样
the singsong eNOS of talking when you go
走路时说话的歌声
really you know so kalbi is an
真的，你知道，所以卡尔比是一个
interesting Java environment for doing
有趣的Java环境
some of that stuff that it's a voice
有些东西是声音
recognition environment that can
可以识别的环境
actually give you some tonal and
实际上给你一些色调，
inflection data from your speaker que al
来自说话者的拐点数据
di yes yeah the the classified that as
di yes yeah the分类为
far as the classifier framework is
就分类器框架而言
concerned the filter bubbler just is
有关过滤器起泡器只是
interested if you go hey classifier
有兴趣的话，您好嘿分类器
here's some text what label do you think
这是一些文字，您认为标签是什么
it is so that it's purposefully very
因此，它是有目的的
generic right so then if you want to use
通用权，所以如果您想使用
a word to Veck kind of implementation or
Veck的实现方式
even like um what's the google frame
甚至就像嗯，什么是Google框架
tensorflow like if you want to have you
张量流就像你想拥有你
know it doesn't even have to be java
知道它甚至不必是Java
javascript you know it just has to
您知道的javascript
result in the JavaScript environment
导致JavaScript环境
getting a label bag I don't I don't read
拿到标签袋我不读
about word Tyvek and I tried playing
关于特卫强一词，我尝试玩
with it a little bit and actually the
用一点点，实际上
there's some really cool stuff that dice
有一些很酷的东西可以切成小方块
comm open sourced for solar the search
comm为太阳能搜索开源
and the Java based search engine to do
和基于Java的搜索引擎
word to Veck in so that if you do stuff
告诉维克，如果你做的话
like if you search for data scientist
就像您搜寻数据科学家一样
you'll get back java jobs because
您将获得Java工作，因为
there's a like a word to Veck
Veck就像一个字
association those that Java and data
关联那些Java和数据
scientists has often a have a
科学家经常有一个
relationship to each other they cool
彼此很酷的关系
there are a oh s and there are iOS and
有一个哦，有iOS和
and Android implementations and there's
和Android实施，
also a native web implementation but
也是本机Web实施，但是
it's kind of the same ideas SWT on
这与SWT的想法相同
Eclipse
日食
which is that you write a program in
那是你在写一个程序
JavaScript it is instantiating native UI
JavaScript，它正在实例化本机UI
peers and then you
同行，然后你
instead of rear like swing rewrote all
而不是像秋千那样后方重写了所有
the UI peers in Java but in in SWT which
UI在Java中是对等的，但在SWT中
is what it clips is written in it
它剪辑的内容就是这样写的
actually uses the native UI peers from
实际上使用来自
the operating system so react native is
操作系统，所以本机反应是
this kind of same idea but for building
这种相同的想法，但对于建筑
UIs with JavaScript so you could I don't
使用JavaScript的用户界面，这样我就不会
know if like I said that's an
知道是否像我说的那样
interesting question I'll look into that
有趣的问题，我会调查一下
and put something up on my website but
并在我的网站上放一些东西
the you should be able to do a if
你应该能够做到
somebody should be doing that would be a
有人应该这样做
cool idea is to do a react native port
好主意是做一个反应本机端口
for Java so that you could take your
Java，这样您就可以
react native application that runs on
对运行在其上的本机应用程序做出反应
iOS and on Android you could just run it
iOS和Android，您可以运行它
on the Java VM and it would be a desktop
在Java VM上，它将是一个桌面
job of the a map location that would be
地图位置的工作
cool so in theory possible like I said I
很酷，所以理论上可能像我说的那样
don't know it seems like the kind of
不知道好像是那种
thing somebody somewhere would have been
某处某人的事
like I'm bored I'm gonna try this so I'm
就像我很无聊，我要尝试这个，所以我
gonna I'm gonna look you buddy else all
我要去看你哥们
right well I guess I'll hand it back to
好吧，我想我会把它交给
our tell it in announcer and host
我们在播音员和主持人中讲
Bruno's hola okay just let me yeah so
布鲁诺的呼啦好吧，就这样吧
thanks again does great um you know
再次感谢你，你知道吗
since we're since we have that's a new
因为我们拥有了那是一个新的
thing that we're here we haven't talked
我们在这里的事情我们还没有谈过
about you know even get his java
关于你知道甚至得到他的java
javascript talk but we do have here with
javascript对话，但我们确实有
us a good friend of ours from Oracle
我们是我们Oracle的好朋友